{
    "subject": "resource/Fallzone",
    "predicate": "ontology/hometown",
    "object": "resource/United_States",
    "human_readable": "Fallzone is from United States.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9643465876579285,
            "question": "Is Fallzone based in the United States?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9545645117759705,
            "question": "Is Fallzone American?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7558519244194031,
            "question": "Where is Fallzone from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5655884742736816,
            "question": "To which country does Fallzone belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5607086420059204,
            "question": "What country is Fallzone associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5058962106704712,
            "question": "What is Fallzone's place of origin?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49524110555648804,
            "question": "From which country does Fallzone hail?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4684273302555084,
            "question": "Can you tell me about Fallzone's origin?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4437483847141266,
            "question": "What nationality is Fallzone?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.37970781326293945,
            "question": "Where might you find information about Fallzone?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Fallzone is from United States.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8825_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What nationality is Fallzone?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8825_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me about Fallzone's origin?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8825_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=From which country does Fallzone hail?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8825_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8825_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8825_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8825_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8825_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8825_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8825_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8825_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8825_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8825_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8825_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nWhile the documents mention FallZone Safety Surfacing serving all 50 states, they don't explicitly state that it's *from* the United States.  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`\n\nThe documents provided contain information about FallZone, a company that provides playground surfacing solutions. The text mentions that FallZone has experience in the industry and serves all 50 states, which implies that the company is based in the United States."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\"output\": \"yes\"}\n```\n\nThe documents mention \"FallZone Safety Surfacing\" and its services provided across the United States, which supports the statement that Fallzone is from the United States."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Several testimonials mention FallZone working with businesses in New Jersey and New York. Additionally, the text states they are a nationwide supplier and installer serving all 50 states.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}